(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting ready...
Lunch with me
作詞/作曲 ヒゲドライバー
Lyrics/Composition: Hige Driver
はやく起きた朝は
On a morning when I wake up early,
なんだかいつもより眠くて
I'm somehow sleepier than usual.
昨日の夜ずっと
All through last night,
漫画を読んでたら眠れなくってさ
I was reading manga and couldn't sleep.
今頃そっちは
I wonder what you're doing,
どこで何してるかななんて
over there, right about now.
考えてたら心が
When I think about it, my heart
ふわっと軽くなるんだ
feels light and airy.
照れくさいんだけど
It's a bit embarrassing, but
昨日読んだ漫画の
the protagonist of the manga I read yesterday
主人公に君がちょっと似て
reminded me a little bit
たんだよ
of you.
ねぇ お昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 一緒に
Hey, let's have lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch together.
食べよう
Let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I want to share the same feelings, even just a little.
そう 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 だけでも
Yes, even if it's just lunch, lunch, lunch.
贅沢なことは望まなくっても
Even if I don't ask for anything extravagant,
いつもの君でいいんだよ
just being your usual self is fine.
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together!
ミステリアスとは
I wouldn't call them exactly
言えない地味な日々だけど
mysterious, just plain days, but
僕らの最近は
lately, for us,
少しキラキラなんだ
things have been a little sparkly.
こんなに直前(まぢか)に
Even if something bad happens
嫌なことあっても
so close to the time,
君に会えると思うとにや
when I think about seeing you,
けちゃってさ
I start grinning.
ねぇ お昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 一緒に
Hey, let's have lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch together.
食べよう
Let's eat!
一人よりもっと楽しくなるから
Because it'll be much more fun than being alone.
そう 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 昼 だけだし
Yes, it's just lunch, lunch, lunch,
特別なことはないから
it's nothing special,
変なこと考えないでよ
so don't get any weird ideas.
待たせにいくけど
I'll keep you waiting, but
知ってるかな
do you know
君がくれる
what you give me?
皆こんねねー！
Hi everyone, Konnene!
本日をもちまして２年目に入りました！
As of today, I've entered my second year!
ホロライブ５期生オレンジ担当
Hololive 5th Generation, in charge of orange,
アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねです！
idol VTuber Momosuzu Nene here!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
さて今日はですねなんと、ステージがコロコロコロコロいっぱい変わるので
Well, today, the stage is going to change a lot,
ちょっと準備が必要なので
so I need some time to prepare.
早速次のステージに移動してからちょっとお話していきたいと思います！
I'll move to the next stage right away and then we can talk!
というわけで、次のステージに変身！
So, transforming to the next stage!
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
はい、というわけで１曲目、ねねのオリジナル曲『Lunch with me』をお聴きいただきました！
Yes, so for the first song, you heard Nene's original song 'Lunch with me'!
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
ちょっと水飲んでくるわ
I'm going to go drink some water.
ふぅ…すごいんよ
Whew... it's amazing.
『Lunch with me』はね、使う消費エネルギーがさ、もう
The energy consumed by 'Lunch with me' is just, well...
ものすごいもんよ
it's really something else.
はぁー！
Haa!
はい！というわけで今日はですね
Yes! So today,
こちらの #Nene1stAnniversary と #ねぽらぼ1周年 の
using these hashtags, #Nene1stAnniversary and #NePolabo1stAnniversary,
タグでよかったらいっぱいスクショとか感想とか
if you'd like, please share lots of screenshots and thoughts.
募集してます。いっぱい呟いてね。
I'm looking for them. Tweet a lot, okay?
見て見て、これ。
Look, look at this.
ゲームセンターのステージに移動してきました。
I've moved to the game center stage.
どう？可愛いでしょ？
How is it? Cute, right?
ちょっと息整えないと次の曲に行けないよ。
I need to catch my breath or I can't move on to the next song.
みんなそういえばあれどうだった？
By the way, how was that?
プレミア公開、『Mr.Music』をみんなで歌いました。
The premiere of 'Mr. Music' that we all sang together.
なんとね、動画作ってくれてるのは、あの、もりぷろの
Actually, the one who made the video is, you know, from MoriPro...
わらびちゃんが作ってくれました！
Warabi-chan made it!
忙しい中本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much even though you were busy!
みんなそれわかった上でもう一回見てくれるよな？
You'll all watch it again knowing that, right?
はい、というわけでねねの息がなんとなく落ち着いてきましたので
Yes, so since Nene's breath has somewhat settled,
次の曲に移ろうと思ったんだけど、もうちょっと休憩しても大丈夫だよって言われたから
I was thinking of moving to the next song, but I was told it's okay to rest a bit more,
もう一回水飲んでから次の曲に移動します。
so I'll drink some water one more time and then move to the next song.
あぁー、
Ahhh,
今回ね、あの、振り入れが
This time, the choreography...
４日間くらいしかなかったの、
I only had about four days.
１週間くらいしか練習できなくて、
I could only practice for about a week,
もうちょっと１曲目から間違えないかめっちゃ不安だったわけなんだけど、
so I was really worried about making a mistake from the first song,
なんとなく上手くいったわ。
but it somehow went well.
よかったよかった。
Good, good.
はい、じゃあ次の曲行こうかな。
Okay, let's go to the next song.
次の曲はこのゲームセンターにぴったりなキャラクターの曲を歌いたいと思います。
For the next song, I'd like to sing a song by a character that's perfect for this game center.
リクエスト多かったんでこれ、よかったらみんなで合いの手して楽しんでください。
Since there were many requests, please enjoy joining in with the chants if you'd like.
それでは次の曲聴いてください、
Now, please listen to the next song:
『かくしん的☆めたまるふぉ～ぜっ！』
'Kakushinteki☆Metamaruphoze!'
食い尽くせ！全身全霊遊び倒せ！
Eat it all! Play with all your soul!
もっと、もっと、楽しめよ乙女
Enjoy it more, more, oh maiden!
みんなに気づかれないように
So that no one notices,
いざゆけ、干物妹ライフ！
Go forth, Himouto Life!
お気に入りのフードかぶり
Donning my favorite hood,
今日も今日とてゴロゴロして
today as well, I'm just idling about.
大好物のポテチを手に
With my favorite potato chips in hand,
パソコンとにらめっこしよ
let's have a staring contest with the PC.
立てば芍薬、座れば牡丹
Standing, she's a peony; sitting, a tree peony.
歩く姿は百合の花
Walking, she's like a lily.
誰もがうらやむ完璧JK
A perfect high school girl everyone envies.
ほら、玄関くぐったら変身だ！
See, once I pass the entrance, I transform!
さあ、食うたら寝よう！
Come on, let's eat and sleep!
いつだってクールに遊ぶのさレコンポ
Always playing it cool with Recompo
ずっと ずっと QEMは友達
Forever and ever, QEM are my friends
お兄ちゃんは厳しいけど
Big brother is strict, but
きっと きっと 許してくれちゃうの
I'm sure, I'm sure he'll end up forgiving me
わがまま放題 大好きの裏返し
Being selfish is just my way of saying I love you
外では猫をかぶり
Putting on an act in public
今日も明日も演じるのです
I'll keep playing the part today and tomorrow
大好評の笑顔を武器に
With my popular smile as my weapon
友達にバレないよう鬼に
I'll become a demon so my friends won't find out
立てば二等親 座れば満丸
Standing, I'm two heads tall; sitting, I'm a perfect circle
歩く姿はちんちくりん
Walking around looking short and cute
誰でも癒やせる愛嬌マスコット
A charming mascot who can heal anyone
さあ限界超えるまでパーティーナイト
Now, let's party all night until we reach our limits
宴の始まりだ
The banquet begins!
ほら乙女かな 女の子演じてみても
See, maybe I'm a maiden? Even if I try to act like a girl
お兄ちゃんだけは騙せない
I can't fool only you, Big Brother
嫌われたくないも 素直に言えない
I don't want you to hate me, but I can't say it honestly
ありがとうを態度で示すわ
I'll show my thanks through my actions
大抵は手厳しいわ 思い通りいかない
Usually you're harsh, things don't go as planned
なんて知る由もない
There's no way for me to know that
なんて一新同体 二人で一つ
Like being of one mind and body, the two of us as one
だって だって それが兄弟でしょ
Because, because that's what being siblings is, right?
一蓮托生 二人きりの運命
Sharing the same fate, just our destiny together
今日だって自由奔放 笑い飛ばせ
Today too, let's laugh off our free-spiritedness
もっと もっと 楽しんだもん勝ち
The more you enjoy it, the more you win
天真爛漫 スマイルで ぎゅっと ぎゅっと
With an innocent smile, I'll tightly, tightly
心を掴んじゃうの
Grab your heart
やりたい放題 信頼の裏返し
Doing whatever I want is just my way of showing trust
はい、おしまい！
That's it!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
「かくしん的☆めたまるふぉ～ぜっ！」お聞きいただきました。
You just heard 'Kakushigoto Maaru Fooze!'
あの、スタッフさん、なんかマイクがガビガビ言ってるから
Um, staff-san, my mic is making a crackling noise,
もしよければあの、チェックしていただけると幸いです。
so if you could please check it, I'd appreciate it.
なんかボチャン、ボチャンって言ってます。
It sounds like 'bochan, bochan'.
ねねの耳がおかしいのかな？
Is something wrong with my ears?
ねねの耳っぽい？
Is it my ears?
ねねのイヤホンの問題っぽいかな？
Is it a problem with my earphones?
あ、みんなちょっとごめんね。
Ah, sorry everyone.
あ、それじゃあ次のステージに移っちゃおうかな？
Oh, should I move to the next stage then?
どうぞ！スタッフさん準備お願いします。
Here we go! Staff-san, please get ready.
ふふ、なんだろう、機嫌不明？
Hehe, what's this? Unknown mood?
お、何も聞こえなくなっちゃった！
Oh, I can't hear anything now!
あ、聞こえた。
Ah, I can hear it.
機嫌不明っぽい！
It seems like an unknown mood!
まあいいか。なんかあったら止めよう。はは。
Well, whatever. If anything happens, I'll stop. Haha.
はい、というわけで次はね、え、ここどのステージか覚えてるみんな？
Alright, so next, do you all remember what stage this is?
ポロポロポロポロ... ラミィの湖に遊びに来てみました！
*Patter, patter...* I've come to visit Lamy's lake!
じゃあここに来たらさ、ねね絶対にやりたかったことがあるんだよ。
Now that I'm here, there's something I absolutely wanted to do.
ちょっとごめんね、雪民さん、先に謝っておく。
I'm sorry, Yukimin, let me apologize in advance.
雪民さん、全世界の雪民さん、ごめんね。
Yukimin, to all the Yukimin in the world, I'm sorry.
あ、なんか、なんか聞こえなくなった。
Ah, I can hear it, I can't hear anything again.
あ、なんか、なんだろうな、なんか雪っぽい！
Ah, it's like, what is it... it feels like snow!
雪っぽい香りがする。
It smells like snow.
この、この柱とかラミィがギュッとしたなんか匂いするわ。
These pillars smell like Lamy gave them a tight hug.
ねねの手垢つけとこ。
I'll leave my handprints on them.
はい、というわけで今ね、マイク見てもらってたんで、なんか大丈夫そうになった。よかったよかった。
Alright, they checked my mic just now, and it seems to be okay. Good, good.
ね、見て、ここに来るとねねめっちゃ幻想的じゃない？なんか。
Hey, look, doesn't Nene look super mystical here? Somehow.
あ、いい！
Ah, nice!
うわー！おおー！やばくないこれ？
Whoa! Ohhh! Isn't this amazing?
映えちゃってるじゃん！
It's so photogenic!
ラミィさすがだな。
Lamy, as expected.
すごい。ねねですら映えるこの湖最高だね。
Incredible. This lake that makes even Nene look good is the best.
あ、いいじゃん。
Oh, that's good.
というわけで、次はこの、とっても幻想的な空間に
So, for the next one, I've brought a song that's
ピッタリの曲を持ってきたので、それを歌っていきたいと思いまーす。
perfect for this very mystical space, and I'd like to sing it.
よいしょよいしょ。
There we go, there we go.
えー、それでは次の曲聴いてください。
Now then, please listen to the next song.
Sincerely。
Sincerely.
知らない言葉を 覚えていくたび
Every time I learn a word I didn't know before,
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
I reach out my hand within the memories.
だけど一人では 分からない言葉も
But there are words that even alone
あるのかもしれない
I might not understand.
「さよなら」は苦くて
"Goodbye" is bitter,
「愛してる」は 遠いにおいがした
and "I love you" had a distant scent.
たとえようのない この想いは
This feeling that cannot be compared
とても怖くて
is very scary,
だけど とても愛おしくて
but also very precious.
私 なんで泣いてるんだろう
I wonder why I'm crying?
心になんて 答えたらいい
How should I answer my heart?
言葉はいつでも 語るでもなくて
Words don't always speak;
そこにあるばかり 募るばかり
they are just there, just building up.
私は あなたに 会いたくなる
I find myself wanting to see you.
きれいな言葉を 覚えていくたび
Every time I learn a beautiful word,
自分のことが 嫌いになりそう
I feel like I might start to hate myself.
だけど背を向けちゃ いけない言葉も
But there might be words
あるのかもしれない
I shouldn't turn away from.
悲しみは冷たく
Sadness is cold,
「ありがとう」は ぬくもりに色づく
and "thank you" is colored with warmth.
形のないもの 触れるたびに
Every time I touch something formless,
あなたの声が 胸の奥で響いているの
your voice echoes deep within my chest.
書きかけてはやめた 宛名のない手紙は
The letter I started writing and then stopped,
風に揺れる
with no addressee, sways in the wind.
届けたい人の街まで
To the town of the person I want to reach,
始まりの終わりを 伝えるために
to tell them of the end of the beginning.
生きること やめないこと
Living, and not giving up,
あなたに今日 誇れるように
so that I can be proud to face you today.
私 なんで泣いてるんだろう
I wonder why I'm crying?
心になんて 答えたらいい
How should I answer my heart?
言葉はいつでも 語るでもなくて
Words don't always speak;
そこにあるばかり 募るばかり
they are just there, just building up.
私は あなたに 会いたくなるよ
I find myself wanting to see you...
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
「Sincerely」をお聞きいただきましたー！
That was "Sincerely"!
はい、じゃあね、
Alright then,
あんまりね、ここに長いし、滞在してると、
if I stay here too long,
雪民さんがね、「俺も、俺も」ってなっちゃっていけないから、ちょっと次のステージいくわね。
the Yukimins might start saying "Me too, me too," so I'll head to the next stage.
せーの！
Ready, set... go!
あー、やっぱここが落ち着くわー。
Ah, I really feel at home here.
よし、ちょっとお水飲むね。
Alright, I'm going to drink some water.
はい、というわけで、今、「Sincerely」をお聞きいただいたんですけど、
Okay, so that was "Sincerely."
どうでしたでしょうか？
How did you like it?
ね、背景とぴったりだったと思わない？
Didn't it fit the background perfectly?
ちょっとまだ、この曲とっても難しかったから、
That song was still very difficult for me,
もっと何回か練習して、もっといい感じに歌えるようになったら、また披露するね。
so I'll practice more and perform it again once I can sing it even better.
ちょっとコメント読んじゃおう。
Let me read some comments.
どれどれ。
Let's see...
えー、「泣いたわー」
"I cried,"
「おかえり」
"Welcome back,"
「実家のような安心感」
"It's as comforting as being at home,"
「最高」
"The best,"
「エモ」
"Emotional,"
「はしゃがなくていいからホームが一番」
"You don't have to be wild, home is best."
え、ここでもはしゃげるからね！
Hey, I can be wild here too, you know!
うわああああああ！
Waaaaaaaaa!
ちょっと次の曲大変な曲だから、
The next song is a tough one,
次の曲大変な曲だから、あんまり暴れないように。
so I shouldn't go too crazy.
「浄化された」って？ありがとう。
"Purified"? Thank you.
え、よかった、似合ってた？
I'm glad. Did it suit me?
これ、心の綺麗な人には見える水だよ。
This is water that only people with pure hearts can see.
見える？
Can you see it?
見えたらいいな。
I hope you can.
いやー、みんなに見えるかなー、どうかなー。
I wonder if everyone can see it or not.
じゃあ、次の曲に行きたいと思うんですけど、
Now, I'd like to move on to the next song,
次の曲は、放送でねねがちょっと匂わせしたんじゃなかったかな、
which I think I teased a bit in a stream...
メン限。メン限だったっけ、なんかの時に、
maybe it was a members-only stream?
「もうほぼそれ答えじゃん」って言われたんだけど、
Someone said, "That's basically the answer."
その匂わせしてた曲をね、今日はなんと全編ね、
That song I was teasing, today I'm performing it,
オリジナルの振り付けでこうやらせていただいてるので、
in its entirety with original choreography!
思い切りやっていきたいと思います。みんなも多分知ってると思う、
I'm going to give it my all. I'm sure you all know it—
有名な曲を元気いっぱいやってくぞー！
a famous song, performed with full energy!
というわけで、次の曲聞いてください、「シル・ヴ・プレジデント」！
So, please listen to the next song: "Sil-V-President"!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let any romantic scandals slide
消してあげる
I'll erase them for you
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
作詞：ナナホシ管弦楽団/作曲：岩見陸
Sil-V-President
Lyrics: Nanahoshi Orchestra / Composition: Iwami Riku
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the president
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
I'll exile any woman who messes with someone else's man
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the president
「嫌、ただの友達だよ」ってごまかす奴は
Anyone who tries to cover it up saying "No, we're just friends"
膝から電気を流します
I'll send an electric shock through their knees
だ・だ・大統領に
Pre-pre-president
敵はセンセーショナル クローズアップ
The enemy is a sensational close-up
だ・だ・独裁
Di-di-dictatorship
やらせて徹底的に幸あれ
Let me do it, and may there be thorough happiness
大嫌い？
You hate it?
興味ない？
Not interested?
苦痛は病気でバイバイバイ
Pain is a disease, bye-bye-bye
権力・財産・地位・名誉
Power, wealth, status, honor
何もないけど裁きたい
I have none of those, but I want to judge
よいしょ、ワン・ツー・スリー
Heave-ho, one, two, three
だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the pre-pre-president
まずは君を捕まえるね
The first thing I'll do is catch you
濡れたタオルで洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything with a wet towel
誰ですかあの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですかそうですか
Is it no good? I see
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let any romantic scandals slide
消してあげます
I will erase them for you
シル・ヴ・プレ・プレ・プレジデント
S'il vous plaît, ple-ple-president
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the president
「嫌、ただの仕事の付き合いだよ」っていう奴は
Anyone who says "No, it's just a business relationship"
二度と働けなくしてやります
I'll make it so they can never work again
宣誓！以下同文。
I swear! Ditto for the rest.
向こうが強引でさって言う男の口には
As for the man who says "She was the aggressive one"
練り消し流し込んで固めてやります
I'll pour kneaded eraser into his mouth and harden it
見・見・見ちゃだめ
Don't-don't-don't look
まるでドファンキー・スキャンダラス
It's just like a funky scandalous thing
待・待・待った
Wait-wait-wait
動向・解消なしの術で
With a technique of no movement or resolution
愛はない？
There's no love?
自由じゃない？
It's not free?
悪くないのでハイ・ハイ・ハイ
It's not bad, so yes, yes, yes
軽薄・堂々・行けシャアシャア
Frivolous and grand, go on shamelessly
何もないとかありえない
Saying there's "nothing" is impossible
よいしょ、ワン・ツー・スリー
Heave-ho, one, two, three
だ・だ・大統領になってもね
Even if I become the pre-pre-president
多分君は止まらないね
You probably won't stop, will you?
知らんとぼけてのらりくらり躱すのね
Feigning ignorance and dodging me noncommittally
ですですかこんばんは
Is that so? Good evening
右ですかそうですか
To the right? I see
情熱は不注意 乱れそう
Passion is carelessness, likely to get messy
消してしまいたい
I want to erase it
ワン・ツー・スリー
One, two, three
だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the pre-pre-president
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll really catch you
濡れたタオルで洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything with a wet towel
どこですか
Where is it?
今、あんた 見てちゃった
Now, I saw you looking
バレちゃった
I got caught
夜道はどうぞ お気をつけて
Please be careful on the night roads
さよなら
Goodbye
代わりに銃声
A gunshot instead
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous Pre-Pre-President
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
シル・ヴ・プレジデント、お聴きいただきました！
You just heard "S'il Vous President"!
大変だ、この曲は。
This song is tough.
あの、長めに曲間とって大丈夫です。終わったんで。
Um, it's okay to take a long break between songs. Since it's over.
あの、長めに曲間とっていいですか、皆さん？
Um, can I take a long break, everyone?
ちょっとね、あの、今日もねっこの方たちに何人か来ていただいてますので、
You see, um, some of the Nekko are here today as well,
ちょっとステージ上に来ていただきたいと思います。
so I'd like to have them come up on stage.
それでは、それでは、ねっこのみんなー！
Now then, now then... Everyone, the Nekko!
逆さで今日は来たのね。
You came upside down today, didn't you?
おー、浮いてるね、今日調子いいね。
Oh, you're floating, you're in good shape today.
可愛い、今日も可愛いよ。
Cute, you're cute today too.
ちょっとねねが水飲む間ちょっとドアップで映っててね。
Stay in a close-up for a bit while Nene drinks some water.
お、仲良しだね。
Oh, you're good friends.
あれ、入れ替え入れ替え。
Oh, swapping places, swapping places.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
ちゅん。ねね。
Chun. Nene.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
これ、あれなのかな。
I wonder if this is...
この子はこのまま次の曲に行けたりしますか？
Can this one stay here for the next song?
あ、本当、じゃあオレンジの子さ、ちょっといてもらおうかな次。寂しいから。
Oh, really? Then maybe the orange one can stay for the next one. Because it'll be lonely otherwise.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
おいで、オレンジの子、今日は君が主役だ。
Come here, orange one, you're the star today.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
おー、お前寂しがりかよ。寂しがりか。おいで。
Oh, are you lonely? Are you? Come here.
イェーイ！
Yay!
あ、よしよし。よしよしよしよし。
Ah, there, there. There, there, there, there.
さあ、シル・ヴ・プレジデントだったんだけどみんなどうだった？
So, that was "S'il Vous President," how did everyone like it?
なんか結構ね、あのねねの歌枠のリクエストありますかって聞いた時に、
Like, quite a bit, um, when I asked if there were any requests for Nene's singing streams,
あの、こないだ上げたグッバイ宣言と一緒にくらい結構リクエストがあって、
um, there were as many requests for this as for "Goodbye Sengen" which I uploaded the other day,
あ、これはね、可愛い曲だし、振り付けありでやりたいなと思ってね、とっておいたんだよ。
so I thought, "This is a cute song, and I want to do it with choreography," so I saved it for today.
みんなどうだった？
How was it, everyone?
ちょっとコメント見に行こう。
Let's go check the comments for a bit.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
え、可愛かった？あ、よかった。
Eh, was it cute? Oh, good.
本当、奇跡的にね、今の一回だけ、あのダンスにそんな、あの、ヤバイミスがなくてね、
Truly, miraculously, just this once, there weren't any, um, terrible mistakes in the dance,
とっても安心してるわ。ヤバかった、マジさっき。
so I'm very relieved. It was bad, really, a while ago.
練習の時ヤバかったの。
It was bad during practice.
白い子アンチみたいになってるよ、だって。
"The white one looks like an anti," they say.
お前、どうしたの、ねねになんか、文句でもあんのか。
Hey, what's wrong? Do you have a problem with Nene or something?
なんやー！
What?!
ちょっと疲れちゃった。
I'm a bit tired.
というわけでねねはですね、今日でなんと、一周年を迎えることができまして、
So, Nene has, amazingly, reached her first anniversary today,
この一年の間にね、昨日も振り返ってたんだけど、本当にたくさんの、あの、夢が叶いまして、
and during this past year, as I was reflecting yesterday, truly many, um, dreams came true,
こんなね、みんなたくさん見てくれるこのステージの中で、歌って踊れること、本当に嬉しく思っています。
and I'm truly happy to be able to sing and dance on this stage with so many of you watching.
いつも準備をいっぱいでしてくれてる、あの今聴いてるであろスタッフのみなさんもありがとうございます。
Thank you also to the staff who are always preparing so much, who are probably listening now.
はい、というわけで、二年目のねねも、いっぱい目標立てたんで、
Yes, so, for Nene's second year, I've set many goals,
お、いいじゃん、これ可愛いじゃん。
Oh, this is good, this is cute.
ねねから葉っぱが生えた。
A leaf sprouted from Nene.
二年目はね、ねねはね、もっと芽が生えて、こいつがグングングングン成長していくように、
In the second year, Nene will sprout more buds, and just as they grow bigger and bigger,
そんな感じになれるように、頑張っていきたいと思います。
I want to work hard so that I can be like that.
あ、みんな呟いてくれてる、これ。
Ah, everyone is tweeting this.
呟いて、#Nene1stAnniversary。
Tweet it: #Nene1stAnniversary.
ね、これプロっぽい発音したんだよ。
See, I used a professional-sounding pronunciation.
ちょっと喋りっぱなしだと息が全然整わない。はじびじょ。
If I keep talking, I just can't catch my breath at all. Seriously a beautiful girl.
お、今日いい感じじゃん。
Oh, looking good today.
今日もビジュがいいね。
Your visuals are good today too.
ねっ子のみんな今日ビジュがいいよ。今日すごい写りがいいわ。
Everyone, you look great today. You're looking very photogenic.
あ、いいよいいよいいよいいよ。
Oh, nice, nice, nice, nice.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
さてさてじゃあ、次の曲にいきたいと思います。
Now then, I'd like to move on to the next song.
次の曲は、ねねの、今日見てる？ママ。
For the next song, are you watching today, Mama?
ねねのママが好きな曲を一曲歌いたいと思います。
I'd like to sing a song that Nene's mama likes.
じゃあ次はね、ちょっと雰囲気に合わせて、
So next, to match the atmosphere,
ねねのこの夜のステージにいきたいと思うので、
I'd like to go to Nene's night stage,
一瞬にして時空を歪めたいと思います。
so I'm going to warp space-time in an instant.
というわけで、カモン、ナイト！
So, come on, night!
ちょっとダサかった今の。
That was a bit uncool just now.
もっとかっこいいのあったかな。
I wonder if there was something cooler?
さ、夜になったので、
Well, now that it's night,
じゃあ次の曲をね、聴いてもらいたいと思いますよ。
I'd like you to listen to the next song.
ねっ子いてもらおう。
I'll have the Nekko stay.
よいしょ。あ、この子いたままにします。
Heave-ho. Oh, I'll keep this one here.
はい。じゃあちょっと大根くんも、バイバイ。
Okay. Well, Daikon-kun, bye-bye.
うわ、めっちゃ不満げ。
Wow, he looks so dissatisfied.
あ、去ってった。
Oh, he's gone.
はい、じゃあ次の曲の準備をしたいと思います。
Okay, now I'll get ready for the next song.
えーっと、真ん中。ん、はい。
Um, the center. Mm, okay.
じゃあ次の曲いきます。えー、次はまた、
Then, here's the next song. For the next one,
しんみりな曲を聴いていただきたいと思います。
I'd like you to listen to a sentimental song.
それでは皆さん聴いてください。未来へ。
Please listen, everyone. 'Mirai e'.
未来へ
作詞/作曲：玉城千春
Mirai e
Lyrics/Music: Chiharu Tamashiro
ほら 足元を見てごらん
Look, look at your feet
これがあなたの歩む道
This is the path you're walking
ほら 前を見てごらん
Look, look ahead
あれがあなたの未来
That is your future
母がくれた
The many kindnesses
SUPER NENECHI STAGE
たくさんの優しさ
that mother gave me
愛を抱いて 歩めと
She repeatedly told me
繰り返した
to walk with love in my heart
あの時はまだ
At that time,
幼くて
I was still young
意味など知らない
and didn't know the meaning
そんな私の手を握り
You took my hand
一緒に歩んできた
and walked together with me
夢はいつも 空高くあるから
Because dreams are always high in the sky
届かなくて 怖いね
it's scary when you can't reach them, right?
だけど追い続けるの
But I'll keep chasing them
自分のストーリー だからこそ
It's my own story, so that's why
諦めたくない
I don't want to give up
不安になると 手を握り
When I feel anxious, you take my hand
一緒に歩んできた
and walked together with me
その優しさを 時には嫌がり
Sometimes I disliked that kindness
離れた 母へ素直になれず
and distanced myself, unable to be honest with mother
ほら 足元を見てごらん
Look, look at your feet
これがあなたの歩む道
This is the path you're walking
ほら 前を見てごらん
Look, look ahead
あれがあなたの未来
That is your future
ほら、コメントも見てごらん。
Look, look at the comments too.
ほら、ねっ子見てごらん。
Look, Nekko, look.
ほらコメントいっぱい。みんなありがとう。
Look at all these comments. Thank you, everyone.
お、お、お、お。
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
その優しさを 時には嫌がり
Sometimes I disliked that kindness
離れた 母へ...
and distanced myself, to mother...
優しさに溢れた
Was filled with kindness
ほら
Look
足元を見てごらん
Look down at your feet
これがあなたの歩む道
This is the path you are walking
ほら
Look
前を見てごらん
Look ahead of you
あれがあなたの未来
That is your future
ほら 足元を見てごらん
Look, look down at your feet
これがあなたの歩む道
This is the path you are walking
ほら 前を見てごらん
Look, look ahead of you
あれがあなたの未来
That is your future
未来へ向かって
Towards the future
ゆっくりと歩いて行こう
Let's walk slowly together
No.1
作詞:shito-Gom/作曲:shito
Lyrics: shito-Gom / Composition: shito
ごめん 憧れてた
Sorry, I looked up to you
追いかけてた
I was chasing after you
いつまでもそうでありたかった
I wanted to be like that forever
完璧なあなた
You, who are so perfect
嫌になった
I grew to hate it
同じように
In the same way
愛もらって
I received love
育ったのに
Even though I was raised
いつからか差が開いてた
Since when did the gap widen?
やつ当たりだって
Even taking it out on others
したかったんだね
Is something I wanted to do
ねえ 神様は試練与えた
Hey, God gave me a trial
「強くなれよ」と
Telling me to "Become strong"
不公平 平等なんて嘘つき
Unfair, equality is just a lie
分かってるけど
I know that, but
可愛いとか 持てたいとか
Being cute, wanting to be popular
諦めないの 女の子だし
I won't give up, I am a girl after all
私らしく猫かぶり
Playing innocent in my own way
お望みはナンバーワンよ
What I want is to be number one
愛してね 生き方は
Please love me, there are
無限にある
Infinite ways to live
お父さんの大袈裟な言葉
Father's exaggerated words
私らしく猫かぶり
Playing innocent in my own way
私らしく行こう
I'll go my own way
暇じゃない人生
A life that isn't idle
生きよう
Let's live it
だって理想言えば キリがなくて
Because if I talk about ideals, there's no end
無い物ねだり 欲しがって
Asking for the impossible, wanting it
鏡を見たって 溜息「はぁ…」
Even looking in the mirror, I sigh "Haa..."
あなただって 悩んでいた
Even you were worried
知らなかった
I didn't know
みんなと同じだと 知った
I realized you're the same as everyone
ピンと張った糸
A string stretched tight
緩んでいく ねえ
Is starting to loosen, right?
ねえ 神様は楽しんでるよ
Hey, God is having fun
予測できない
I can't predict
他人を私は それ以上に
Others, and I will
楽しんでやるぜ
Have even more fun
勉強とか お仕事とか
Studying, working
諦めないの 女の子だし
I won't give up, I am a girl after all
元気よく 愛想よく
Being energetic and friendly
たまにはクールに ついてきて
Sometimes follow me coolly
愛した分 愛されるの
Being loved as much as you love
お母さんがくれたアドバイス
The advice Mother gave me
張り切って ミスしても
Even if I'm eager and make a mistake
私らしく行こう
I'll go my own way
胸張って生きる
Living with my head held high
さらけ出せば 心が温まってたんだ
By laying it all bare, my heart was warmed
好きでいてよ 痛くない
Please like me, it doesn't hurt
神様は夢与えた
God gave me a dream
変われるために
so I could change.
3Q(サンキュー)の糧やるよ
I'll make it food for my "thank yous"
最後まで付き合ってもらうよ
and have you stay with me until the end.
雨はやんで傘を閉じた
The rain stopped, and I closed my umbrella.
今まで見えてなかった景色
A scenery I'd never seen before...
透明が反射して
Reflections in the clarity
世界を照らした
lit up the world.
胸躍る 可愛いくとか持っていたいとか
My heart dances... I want to be cute and all that,
諦めないの女の子だし
I won't give up, 'cause I'm a girl.
私らしく 猫かぶり
In my own way, playing innocent...
ナンバーワンでしょう 愛してね
I'm number one, right? Love me!
生き方は不機嫌にある
Life lies in grumpiness,
お父さんの大袈裟な言葉
the exaggerated words of a father.
いじらしく 猫かぶり
Lovably, playing innocent...
私らしく 行こう
I'll go in my own way.
暇じゃない人生
Life isn't a leisure,
いきよう
let's live it!
ありがとうございました！「No.1」をお聞きいただきました！
Thank you so much! You just heard "No.1"!
というわけで 次が最後の曲に なってしまうんですけど ステージを移動して行きたいと思います
And so, the next one will be the last song, but first, I'm going to move to another stage!
よっこらしょー！
Heave-ho!
お水飲んでいい？
Can I have some water?
これね なんだろう あの 見た目以上に すごい 消費エネルギーの高いダンスだった
This stage... how should I put it? More than it looks, the dance takes a lot of energy!
というわけで 今もお伝えしたんですけど 次で最後の曲になります
Anyway, like I just said, the next one is the last song.
これが終わりましたら ねねからのお知らせが 1個、2個、3個、3個かな？ ありますので
After this is over, I have some announcements... one, two, three... three of them, I think?
よかったら最後まで見ていってね
So please stay tuned until the very end!
というわけで このステージなんだけど これねねのさ あの 桃の木の
Now, about this stage... this is Nene's... peach tree...
並木... なんて言うの？ 並木空？ 並木通り？ 並木？ 森林。
row of trees... what do you call it? Row of trees sky? Row of trees street? Row of trees? Forest.
なんか ねねの森なんだけど この森に あの すごい ぴったりのね
Well, it's Nene's forest, and there's a song that's just perfect for this forest...
まだみんなには一回も
one that I haven't shown any of you yet.
一回も鼻歌すらしたことない曲を今日は みんなに聞いてもらいたいと思います
I haven't even hummed it before! Today, I'd like everyone to hear it.
すごいね 歌詞が ねねと みんなと そしてこの1周年
The lyrics are just perfect for Nene, for all of you, for this 1st anniversary,
そして次の2周年目に向けて ぴったりの曲だと思いまので
and for the upcoming 2nd year... I think it's the perfect song,
よかったら 聞いてね
so please give it a listen!
耳の なんかゴミ全部取ってから聞いてね
Make sure you clean out your ears before listening!
はい。というわけで ちょ 緊張するな 緊張するけど 聞いてね
All right then. Man, I'm nervous... I'm nervous, but please listen.
すごくダンスが難しくて この曲 一番苦労したんだよ
The dance is very difficult, I struggled with this one the most.
なんか ちょっとイメージとしては なんか こう なんだろうな バレリーナっぽい
My image for it is, how should I say it... a bit like a ballerina.
そういう なんか おしとやかなねねを あの 堪能してください
Please enjoy a more graceful Nene.
というわけで 定位置に付きます。 お水を飲みます。
And now, I'll take my position. Let me have some water.
はい、というわけで それでは聞いてください 初披露の曲 「モモノネ」
Okay, here we go. Please listen. This is the first performance of "Momonone."
モモノネ
作詞作曲 ヒゲドライバー
Momonone
Lyrics & Composition: Hige Driver
いくつもの 夢という花が
A multitude of flowers called dreams...
この星には 咲いていたんだ
were blooming on this planet.
自分もきっと 憧れては 思い切り 葉を広げたんだ
I surely yearned for them too, and spread my leaves as wide as I could.
そう 不安な時も いつも支えてくれてたね
Yes, even in anxious times, you were always there to support me.
だからきっと もっと大きくなれる
So I'm sure I can grow even bigger now.
思いは...
My feelings...
まっすぐ伸びて行け
Go straight and grow tall
あの空に届くように
So that it reaches that sky
もう怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore
目一杯咲かせるよ
I'll make it bloom with all my might
自分という名の大きな花
A big flower named "me"
満開のモモノネ
Momonone in full bloom
いくつもの夢という花が
Many flowers called dreams
つぼみのまま咲くのを待ってる
Are waiting to bloom from their buds
雨の中でも風の中でも
Even in the rain, even in the wind
大事に大事に育ててきた
I've raised them carefully, so carefully
しぼんじゃいそうな時も
Even when I feel like I'm about to wither
たくさん元気をくれるねっ子
The Nekko give me so much energy
だからまだ全然枯れたりしない
So I won't wither at all just yet
想いは太陽の光浴びて
My feelings bathe in the sunlight
鮮やかに輝くよ
And shine brilliantly
空を全部覆うほど
Enough to cover the whole sky
目一杯この両手
With these hands spread
広げてさ
Out as wide as possible
みんながいればなんでもできるよ
With everyone here, I can do anything
想いはまっすぐ伸びて行け
May my feelings go straight and grow tall
あの空に届くように
So that they reach that sky
もう怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore
目一杯咲かせるよ
I'll make it bloom with all my might
みんなで咲かそうたくさんの花
Let's all make many flowers bloom
満開のモモノネ
Momonone in full bloom
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
というわけで、初披露の曲、えー、「モモノネ」を聴いていただきました。
And so, you just heard the first performance of my song "Momonone".
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How did you like it?
この曲、なんと思ったみんな？
Everyone, what did you think of this song?
なんと思った？詳細知りたいでしょ？
What did you think? You want to know the details, right?
知りたいでしょ？知りたいでしょ？
You want to know, don't you? You want to know?
というわけで、この曲の詳細と、ねねからのお知らせ2つを紹介するために、
So, to introduce the details of this song and two announcements from Nene,
ステージを移動していきたいと思いますので、
I'm going to move to a different stage.
ちょっと長めなんだけど、
It'll take a little while, but...
みんな今日もね、あのスタッフさんたちがねっ子を使って寸劇作ってくれましたので、
...the staff members have put together a short skit using the Nekko today as well,
みんなちょっと考えながら見てみてね。
So please watch it and try to guess what's happening.
というわけで、レッツゴー！
And with that, let's go!
はい、というわけで、先ほどお聞きいただきました曲の、詳細を発表したいと思います！
Alright, then, I'd like to announce the details of the song you just heard!
ドーン！
Ta-da!
桃鈴ねね 3rd single『モモノネ』！
Momosuzu Nene's 3rd single, "Momonone"!
今日、この日付が変わった、0時00分から配信開始になります。イェーイ！
Digital distribution will start today at midnight, once the date changes. Yay!
なんと今回は、作詞・作曲・編曲、ヒゲドライバーさんにお願いをしました！ありがとうございます！
For this song, Hige Driver-san handled the lyrics, composition, and arrangement! Thank you so much!
そして、なんとね、今回もねねがジャケットのイラストを描いて、
And guess what, Nene drew the jacket illustration again this time...
ちょっとこの『モモノネ』に合った衣装を考えたくて、すごい時間かけてこのジャケットを描きました。
...as I wanted to design an outfit that fits "Momonone," so I spent a lot of time drawing it.
そしてね、この『モモノネ』っていう文字と、この、なんか散らばってるマークもねねが今回考えました。もう、すごい愛が溢れてるでしょ？
Also, Nene came up with the "Momonone" lettering and those scattered marks too. It's overflowing with love, isn't it?
どう？どう？みんな。どうだった？
What do you think? How was it, everyone?
この曲さ、みんな、ねねがこんなゼーハーゼーハーの息で歌ってるやつじゃなくて、ちゃんとしたの聞きたいですよね。ちゃんとしたの。
Regarding this song, I'm sure everyone wants to hear a proper version, not one where Nene is huffing and puffing like this. A proper one.
あ、戻してもらって大丈夫です。よいしょ。ちゃんとしたの聞きたいですよね。
Ah, you can switch the screen back now. Heave-ho. You want to hear the proper version, right?
そんなみんなのために！22時15分からのプレミア公開で、なんと、『モモノネ』のフルMV公開！イェーイ！
For all of you, we're having a premiere at 10:15 PM, and guess what—the full MV for "Momonone" will be released! Yay!
なんと、MVのイラストを描いたのは、誰だったんたって？
And who do you think drew the illustrations for the MV?
え、え、え、ねねだー！
Eh? Eh? Eh? It was Nene!
ねねがね、もう自分のすごい1年の集大成、1年の締めくくり、1年の終演を込めまして、あの、すごい気合入れて描きました。
Nene put her heart and soul into it, as the culmination, the conclusion, and the finale of this amazing year, and drew it with all her might.
そして、時間ない中で一生懸命動画を作ってくださったので、それをね、みんなにフルで見てもらいたくて、
And since the video was created with so much effort despite the limited time, I want everyone to see it in full...
22時15分からプレミア公開をとってます。よかったらそちらも遊びに来て、ねねのこの『モモノネ』のね、あの曲の良さを一緒に知っていただければと思います。
...so we've scheduled the premiere for 10:15 PM. Please come join us and discover how great Nene's song "Momonone" is.
なんとね、そのMVの歌詞を、なんか下にさ、歌詞が出るじゃんか。MVって、こう、横とかに。
And you know how lyrics appear at the bottom or side in MVs?
そのMVに出てくる文字、全部ねね！もう、イラストねね、歌ねね、文字ねね、ジャケットねね。動画は動画師さん。
All the text in that MV is by Nene! The illustrations, the singing, the text, the jacket—all Nene! The video was done by the video creator.
もうすごい愛込めちゃったので、よかったら一緒にみんなで見ましょう。ねねも放送終わったら遊びに行きます。
I've put so much love into it, so let's all watch it together. Nene will be joining after the stream too.
すごいでしょ？すごいでしょ？すごいでしょ？
Amazing, right? It's amazing, isn't it?
頑張ったでしょ？そうでしょ？みんな. だから来てね、みんな。遊びに来て。
I worked hard, didn't I? Right, everyone? So please come. Come join us.
手書きいいでしょ？愛が込もってる感じするでしょ？
Handwritten is nice, right? You can feel the love in it, can't you?
はい、そしてそして、昨日のラミィからのお知らせがあったと思うんですけど、ねねからも1周年を記念したグッズが出ます。
Alright, and moving on, I'm sure you saw Lamy's announcement yesterday, but Nene is also releasing 1st anniversary commemorative goods.
すごいね、リクエストが多かったあれとあれが出ますので、よかったら今から詳細発表するね、みんなドキドキワクワクで見てください。
Those two items that were highly requested are coming out, so I'll announce the details now. Everyone, look forward to it with excitement!
というわけで、桃鈴ねね1周年記念のグッズ、こちら！ドーン！
So, here are Momosuzu Nene's 1st anniversary goods! Ta-da!
活動1周年記念、桃鈴ねねのグッズは、なんと！記念ボイスが2種類！記念グッズが2種類！
For the 1st anniversary, Momosuzu Nene's goods include two types of commemorative voices and two types of commemorative goods!
え、なんと念願の抱き枕と、ねっこのぬいぐるみです！イェーイ！
And, it's my long-awaited body pillow and a Nekko plushie! Yay!
そしてフルセットには、ねねの、えーっと、手書きのメッセージ入りの描き下ろしのポストカードが付きます。詳細見てもらいたいんで、一個ずつゆっくり見ていきましょう。
And the full set comes with a newly drawn postcard featuring a handwritten message from Nene. I want you to see the details, so let's look at them one by one.
活動一周年記念フルセット
Activity 1st Anniversary Commemorative Full Set
そんな感じで！すごい、みんな見たいでしょ？もっとじっくり見たいでしょ？
Just like that! It's amazing, you all want to see it, right? You want a closer look, right?
というわけで、まず抱き枕、こちら！
So, first up, here's the body pillow cover!
見て、抱き枕！もう、ざんままに今のホロライブでできる限界のエッチで描いてくださいって発注した結果、こうなりました。
Look, the body pillow! I asked Zan-mama to draw it with the maximum level of sexiness allowed in Hololive today, and this is the result.
なかなか見れない、ねねが上着をちゃんと締めてる姿と、もう、ボロンボロンのビヨンビヨンに全部出てる姿を描いてもらいました。
She drew Nene in a rare state with her jacket properly closed, and another state where... well, it's all loose and showing everything.
よかったらこのあと出る詳細ページでご確認ください。
Please check the details page that will be up later.
概要欄にあるのかな？マネちゃん、概要欄？
Is it in the description? Manager-chan, is it there?
あ、ありがとうございます！はい、概要欄にあります。よかったら見てください。
Oh, thank you! Yes, it's in the description. Please take a look.
そして次、こちら！
And next, this!
ねっこのぬいぐるみ！
Nekkko Plushie!
これもみんな、すごい可愛い。
Everyone, this is also so cute.
ねねこれサンプルで一個もらったんだけど、一個じゃちょっと足りない、部屋に三個くらい置きたい。
I got one sample, but one isn't enough; I want to put about three in my room.
もうこれ絶対みんな手に入れてほしい、ねね、これ。これみんな絶対、絶対絶対これ、
I really want everyone to get this. Everyone, absolutely, absolutely get this,
これだけでもいいから、これだけでもいいから！もうすごい、すごい可愛くなっちゃったから。
even if it's just this one! It turned out so incredibly cute.
ねっこのぬいぐるみ、ざんままもね、『ねっこのぬいぐるみほしいやんな』って言ってて、
Zan-mama also said, 'You want a Nekkko plushie, don't you?'
形にしちゃいました！
and so we made it a reality!
そして、次！
And next!
え、フルセットの購入特典で、ねねの描き下ろしのポストカード、
As a full set purchase bonus, a postcard drawn by Nene,
そしてメッセージはまだ秘密のメッセージ入りのポストカードがついてきます。
and it comes with a postcard containing a message that's still a secret.
このイラストはもう今回限定なので、ねねね、自分のイラストをグッズにするのってすごい夢だったんだけど、
This illustration is limited to this occasion. It's been a big dream of mine to have my own drawings turned into merch,
まずここでね、ポストカードにしてもらって夢一個叶えちゃいましたんで、
so by having this made into a postcard, I've fulfilled one of my dreams.
よかったらこちらも絶対絶対手に入れてね。
So please make sure to get this too.
ね、といつでも一緒にいよう！
Let's be together always!
はぁ、というわけで、プレミア公開と新曲とグッズのお知らせでした。
Phew! And so, that was the announcement for the premiere, the new song, and the merch.
というわけで、今日はこれで終わりになってしまいます。
And with that, today's stream comes to an end.
みんな、2年目のねねもよろしくね！というわけで、バイバイ！
Everyone, please look forward to Nene's second year too! So, bye-bye!
アンコール！おい！アンコール！おい！
Encore! Hey! Encore! Hey!
アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
わー！アンコールありがとうございます！桃鈴ねねです！
Wow! Thank you for the encore! It's Momosuzu Nene!
みんなアンコールありがとう！というわけで、ねねといえばあの曲、まだ歌ってなかったよね！
Thank you for the encore, everyone! And so, speaking of Nene, I haven't sung *that* song yet, have I?
というわけで、最後の最後に聞いていただきたいと思います。みんな今日は見てくれてありがとう！
So, I'd like you to listen to it as the very last one. Thank you for watching today!
明日はね、ししろんの一周年記念があるよ、みんなぜひチェックしてね！
Tomorrow is Shishiron's 1st anniversary, so make sure to check that out too!
というわけで、ねねねねねねねねねね！大爆走！
So, Nenenenenenene! Daibakuso!
うーっ、ね！
Woo, Ne!
みんな、今日はありがとう！ねねのために一時間使ってくれてありがとうね！
Everyone, thank you for today! Thank you for spending an hour with Nene!
グッズも新曲もチェックよろしくお願いします！飛んでねー！
Please check out the merch and the new song! Fly away!
ハラ・イブ五世　オレンジ担当　桃鈴ねねです
Hara-ibu V, in charge of Orange, Momosuzu Nene.
異世界から来ました　アイドル志望の　新人VTuber
A rookie VTuber and aspiring idol who came from another world.
ま、とにかく明るくいきましょう　ちょっとくらい緊張したって　スベったって
Well, let's just stay cheerful. Even if I'm a bit nervous or if things fall flat...
いい、って感じさ　やっていこう　諦めの悪さは　長所だよね
It's fine. Let's do this. Persistence is a virtue, right?
ねねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene...
んなこともあるけど　悔しいこともあるけど
Things like that happen, and there are frustrating times too...
大丈夫　今日も　しっかりおめかしして
But it's okay. Today, I've dressed up nicely again.
いつかは君と　せーの！　スーパー・エナジー！
One day, with you... One, two! Super Energy!
付いてきてねねねねねねねねねね
Follow me-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne...
全力で行こうぜ　全開で行こう　思い切りやれば　何とかなるよ
Let's go all out, at full throttle. If you give it your all, it'll work out somehow.
ポンコツだっていい　ドジったっていい　ただ駆け抜けていこうぜ
It's okay to be a klutz or to mess up. Let's just keep running through.
ねねねねねね　大・爆・走！
Nenenenene... Daibakuso!
みんなー！ありがとう！アイドルでありがとうみんな、コメント見えてるよー！
Everyone! Thank you! Thank you for letting me be an idol, I can see your comments!
アイスと炭酸とお菓子 揃えて準備OK
Ice cream, soda, and snacks, I've got them all ready—OK!
でも朝は苦手 夜も苦手
But I'm no good in the mornings, or the nights.
やっぱり睡眠て大事だよね
Sleep really is important, after all.
ねねねねねねねね
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne
たくさんの人に愛されい
I wanna be loved by lots of people!
チュッチュッチュ チュッチュッチュ
Chu-chu-chu, chu-chu-chu!
2年目もみんなに愛されい
I wanna be loved by everyone in my second year too!
チュッチュッチュ チュッチュッチュ
Chu-chu-chu, chu-chu-chu!
さあ さらなる高みへ 大爆走ねねち
Now, to even greater heights, Great Runaway Nenechi!
やっちゃって ねねねねねねねね
Let's do it! Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne, Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne
全力で行こうぜ 全開で行こう コンサは誰にも負けたくないだ
Let's go with all our might! Full throttle! I don't want to lose to anyone in concert!
大きな声で 明日の前に
With a loud voice, before tomorrow...
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね
I'm just gonna go to the toilet for a bit, okay?
レッツゴータイム！
Let's go time!
あぁ本当にトイレ行きたい！
Ah, I really want to go to the toilet!
みんな今日は本当にありがとう 最後な最後まで楽しんでね！
Everyone, thank you so much for today! Please enjoy until the very end!
なななな なななな せー
Na-na-na-na, na-na-na-na, ready—
にににに ににじゃなくて
Ni-ni-ni-ni, it's not Ni-ni...
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくて
Nu-nu-nu-nu, it's not Nu-nu...
のののの ののじゃなくて
No-no-no-no, it's not No-no...
ただいま！
I'm back!
最後に ねねねねねねねね
Finally! Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne
ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne, Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne
全力で行こうぜ 全開で行こう 思い切りやればなんとかなるよ
Let's go with all our might! Full throttle! If you give it your all, things will work out!
バカだっていい ドジだっていい ただ駆け抜けていこうぜ
It's okay to be stupid, it's okay to be clumsy, let's just run right through!
ね！ね！ね！ね！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne!
大爆走！
Great Runaway!
それじゃ本当にまたねね！
Well then, see you Nene for real!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
桃鈴ねね 1st Anniversary 3D LIVE
8/13 21:00(JST) ~ START
Momosuzu Nene 1st Anniversary 3D LIVE